<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ugur</title><link>https://rugu.dev/tr/blog/</link><description>Recent content on ugur</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>tr</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rugu.dev/tr/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On the Importance of Typing Fast</title><link>https://rugu.dev/tr/blog/on-typing-fast/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.dev/tr/blog/on-typing-fast/</guid><description>It is often mentioned that the bottleneck in building software projects is not one&amp;rsquo;s typing ability but ability to think clearly and logically, and to design and organize the architecture effectively. Afterall, programing is more than just typing. If it was just typing we would expect to see the difference between in terms of the time and effort required for rewriting an already existing project with that of creating it from scratch for the first time to be too small.</description></item><item><title>My Experience on Switching to Arch Linux</title><link>https://rugu.dev/tr/blog/switching-to-archlinux/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.dev/tr/blog/switching-to-archlinux/</guid><description>About a year ago, I was invited to a pair coding session at the startup where I was working. The developers were receiving consultancy from a strange person. At one point, he took control of the screen sharing while reviewing some of the pull requests that had been made to our codebase. When he shared his screen, there was nothing but a black screen. Suddenly, a terminal screen appeared with his keystrokes and he quickly began examining the codebase, providing feedback on people&amp;rsquo;s code at a speed I had never seen before.</description></item><item><title>An Argument for Idealism</title><link>https://rugu.dev/tr/blog/idealism-argument/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.dev/tr/blog/idealism-argument/</guid><description>This essay was originally written for the &amp;lsquo;Introduction to Philosophy I&amp;rsquo; (PHIL103) course at Bilkent University, where we delved into various branches of philosophy, including consciousness. It reflects some of the thought processes that arose as I grappled with these philosophical questions. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this essay is not an exact reflection of my personal beliefs, but rather an exercise in argumentation.
Despite this, I believe the arguments presented in this essay hold value and are worth exploring.</description></item></channel></rss>